<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
  <identifier>BaseballSlugger</identifier>
  <mediatype>software</mediatype>
  <collection>ipaarchive</collection>
  <description>Baseball seems like an easy game to simulate, but there are nuances in the pitching and batting that can severely hinder the game’s playability if they’re done poorly. Homerun Battle 3D does not encompass the entire sport, focusing instead solely on batting. It’s too bad, because with its smooth presentation and excellent controls, it could easily be a full-fledged arcade baseball experience.&lt;br /&gt;
This is a Home Run Derby game, plain and simple, so its scope is inherently limited, which may turn off those who are looking for a fuller take on the sport. But what it does, it does well.&lt;br /&gt;
There are four modes of play (Training, Classic, Arcade, and Match-Up), although you’re likely to spend all of your time playing only the latter two. Training teaches you the ropes and lets you gain experience with the controls and various pitching styles (nine in all, including changeup, knuckle, sinker, and split). Classic mode is a straight-up Home Run Derby, awarding you solely for home runs hit.&lt;br /&gt;
Arcade mode is where the real action is, awarding you points based on the type of ball hit, distance achieved, and even hitting the wall if it’s not knocked out of the park. There are at least fifty “missions” to complete with varying parameters to be met.&lt;br /&gt;
The better you do, the more extra items you’ll be able to unlock to enhance your character, and these can affect your performance. You can customize your player’s clothes (jersey, pants, facial ware, etc.), facial features and equipment. With 114 unique elements to unlock, you should be able to make a customized avatar to your liking.</description>
  <scanner>Internet Archive HTML5 Uploader 1.6.3</scanner>
  <subject>iOS</subject>
  <subject>games</subject>
  <subject>sports</subject>
  <title>Baseball Slugger - Home Run Race 3D</title>
  <publicdate>2018-09-05 14:20:02</publicdate>
  <uploader>axelm.84@gmx.de</uploader>
  <addeddate>2018-09-05 14:20:02</addeddate>
  <curation>[curator]validator@archive.org[/curator][date]20180905142726[/date][comment]checked for malware[/comment]</curation>
  <creator>Com2uS</creator>
  <date>2009</date>
  <year>2009</year>
  <backup_location>ia906801_22</backup_location>
  <collection>phonesoftware</collection>
</metadata>
